jobscdc.com 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy - JobsCDC - Lowongan Kerja Terbaru November 2017 | BUMN CPNS 2017

**Advertisements**

---  
Jobscdc.com  
  
Like many other web sites, JobsCDC makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes IP (internet protocol) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit JobsCDC. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

JobsCDC does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense .

JobsCDC utilizes certain services from Google for ad serving and web traffic analysis. Please review Google’s privacy policy for more information on how Google AdSense and Google Analytics stores your personal information. These Google services may place and read cookies on your browser, or use web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on the JobsCDC website. Additionally, Google uses the DART cookie to enables it to serve ads to based on your visits to JobsCDC and other sites on the internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on JobsCDC send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, javascript, or web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

JobsCDC has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. JobsCDC’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. (15/06)

**Notes :**

**JobsCDC.com** now available on android device. Download now on Google Play [**here**](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.jobscdc.com). **Please be aware of recruitment fraud.** The entire stage of this selection process is free of charge. **[Privacy Policy - JobsCDC](http://www.jobscdc.com/2011/06/jobscdc-privacy-policy.html)** will never ask for fees or upfront payments for any purposes during the recruitment process such as transportation and accommodation.
